But I had some victories, so
this martini glass, there's
a thing in the book called
the martini principle,
which is the idea that kind
of, if you never want to be alone,
just start to mix a martini because
somebody will jump out from behind a tree
and say that's not how you mix a martini.
And so the way that you know, the
way to find out whether
you're doing something
wrong or not is to start doing it
because somebody will jump out.
But what I wanted is, there's a chapter
in the book called Chapter Ship.
And I wanted this chapter, I
wanted a skull and crossbones
on here, because it's a pirate ship.
In the book it's a pirate ship.
And so I sent them an icon that
had a skull and crossbones,
but they just put
the skull on. I've got no idea why.
And so I can't figure out whether
that's more badass or just annoying.
But the point I'm making is that
kind of, you get to a point where you
lose control.